I love when y'all come in my DMs and say things like, you need to take a break, like you're going to pay my bills.
That's the part for me. I'd be like, are you donating?
Let me know. I would love to take a break.
I tried to take a break this weekend, but again, I don't have agents.
I don't have publicists, so I have to be very mindful now about money in a way that I didn't have to before
because I had more access to it because I was working in other places.
But now I'm completely independent, so I can't just spend like that, right?
So I said, I'm going to take a trip, but I'm going to do it on very, very, very, very, very meager funds.
Let me show y'all where I stay.
We require very meager accommodations.
I feel like y'all be forgetting that, like, can you take a break?
Most of you can't take a break either, can you?
So I will be at the San Diego Laugh Factory this weekend.
Okay, I will be at the San Diego Laugh Factory this weekend doing four shows.
So the best way you can support me is not to tell me to take a break, but to buy tickets.
Ba-dum-bum!